{  
   "ques":[  
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"10 days ago",
         "question":"can you fit make up brushes in the trays",
         "answerType":"Y",
         "answer":"yes it comes with adjustable dividers, you can place the dividers wherever you like..customize your makeup kit however you like it. i have my Mac brushes and eyeshadows on the top shelves and my Mac foundation bottles on the bottom"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Mar 3, 2015",
         "unixTime":1425369600,
         "question":"Can you move all the dividers?",
         "answerType":"?",
         "answer":"yes,all the provided dividers are adjustable"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Dec 30, 2014",
         "unixTime":1419926400,
         "question":"is the surface in side the smooth?",
         "answerType":"Y",
         "answer":"Yes"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Jul 13, 2014",
         "unixTime":1405234800,
         "question":"How deep do the extending trays measure?",
         "answer":"Hi there, Not too deep. Maybe like an inch deep by 2 inches wide, on average. And most of the trays are the same size and cannot be extended or reconfigured in any way. That's my one gripe with this box. Hope this helps!"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"May 21, 2014",
         "unixTime":1400655600,
         "question":"Can bottles of nail polish stand upright in the top trays when the case is closed?",
         "answerType":"?",
         "answer":"No. We just tried it and it won't."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Feb 25, 2014",
         "unixTime":1393315200,
         "question":"what are the Weight?",
         "answer":"Light box. Carry it anywhere."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Dec 3, 2013",
         "unixTime":1386057600,
         "question":"What are the dimensions?",
         "answer":"I'm not sure but it ia good quality."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"602260074X",
         "answerTime":"Jul 23, 2013",
         "unixTime":1374562800,
         "question":"What are the tray size dimensions please? Height - width - depth (how deep is the tray please). I need to know how deep the trays are because I have some taller items that I'd like to store in the case. It isn't stated. Thank you.",
         "answer":"There are 4 trays when the box is open wide. They are each 12 inches long, 4 inches wide. You can make smaller individual sections with the inserts provided within the 12 inch range."
      },
      {  
         "answer":"good",
         "asin":"7800558258",
         "answerTime":"18 days ago",
         "question":"how can I get a product manual copy or electronic copy",
         "questionType":"open-ended"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"7800558258",
         "answerTime":"Feb 28, 2015",
         "unixTime":1425110400,
         "question":"I have used the PE-901P. How does the D-901P compare?",
         "answer":"Thanks for your question. They are same item. Thank you"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"7800558258",
         "answerTime":"May 28, 2014",
         "unixTime":1401260400,
         "question":"goodnight crompre an east electrocautery, and I brought it to Argentina, I want to know how many volts have to be plugged, because we have 220 &#x200B;&#x200B;here.",
         "answer":"I own this unit and live in the USA so whatever that is, it works here. There are virtually no instructions or directions!! Good Luck."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"7800558258",
         "answerTime":"Jan 30, 2014",
         "unixTime":1391068800,
         "question":"Does it work for pedal? Thank you",
         "answerType":"N",
         "answer":"No it doesn't the way it comes. You have to push the on off button."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"7800558258",
         "answerTime":"Nov 6, 2013",
         "unixTime":1383724800,
         "question":"does it come with everything shown in the pictures",
         "answerType":"Y",
         "answer":"Yes"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"9788071813",
         "answerTime":"Jun 10, 2014",
         "unixTime":1402383600,
         "question":"how i know if the perfume or eau de toylette for men or women is real or not fake? If the perfume is fake they should be clear is fake or say it is not original and it is original but in the website you don't know.",
         "answer":"Why are you asking it? I think they don't sell fake products or people will negative the seller."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"9788071813",
         "answerTime":"Apr 23, 2014",
         "unixTime":1398236400,
         "question":"Is this product in an unopened box? like the one that we would get in a store?",
         "answer":"Yes, it's perfect! unopened box"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"9788071813",
         "answerTime":"Apr 23, 2014",
         "unixTime":1398236400,
         "question":"Is it in an original packaging?",
         "answerType":"?",
         "answer":"s est en el paquete original. Saludos"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Aug 15, 2013",
         "unixTime":1376550000,
         "question":"how hard is it to install?",
         "answer":"It's very easy to install. It arrives fully assembled, so there's nothing to put together. The manufacturer provides a small tube of silicone glue, but it's really just silicone in a tube. I had some silicone lying around my workshop, so I just used that and my caulking gun to apply a generous amount of clear silicone to the back of the unit. The main thing to get right is the cleanliness of the surface to which you are mounting the unit. It must be clean and free of gunk, soap scum, wax, or any other gooey stuff. I scrubbed my tile with Ajax; rinsed, dried, and then cleaned again with alcohol. With a clean surface you\"ll get a good strong bond. Position the unit to the location and height you prefer. Apply a couple of big gobs to the back of the unit and press firmly against the mounting surface. Hold in place for a minute or two. I like to place three or four lengths of painting tape over the unit to hold it in place overnight. Remove tape carefully the next day, and you should have a great bond."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Dec 6, 2014",
         "unixTime":1417852800,
         "question":"Can I mount this unit on a fiberglas shower wall that is smooth &amp; shiny? Better wiith the silicone method or the command strips?",
         "answer":"I just used the command strips & even with showering everyday, after almost a year they are still good and tight. No problems at all."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Jun 12, 2014",
         "unixTime":1402556400,
         "question":"Are the chambers easy to refill from a bulk size container? (Mine are gallon size, opening about the same size as a jug of milk)",
         "answerType":"?",
         "answer":"I have the four-chamber dispenser. I find them easy to refill since you can remove the chambers and pull the cap off the top of them."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Oct 10, 2014",
         "unixTime":1412924400,
         "question":"My spouse is worried that mold will grow around and/or inside the unit. Have people experienced this issue? If so how did you address it? Thanks!",
         "answer":"It opens easy to clean. Have had no problems with it, but I do not have a mold issue in my bathroom."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Dec 5, 2014",
         "unixTime":1417766400,
         "question":"Can you put oils in it--such as pre-shave, body oils?",
         "answerType":"Y",
         "answer":"Yes anything liquid can be used in the dispenser"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"yes/no",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Mar 13, 2014",
         "unixTime":1394694000,
         "question":"I've heard that because conditioner is much thicker than shampoo, it does not dispense well; has anyone found that to be true?",
         "answerType":"?",
         "answer":"Thicker substances like Conditioner, Dandruff Shampoo, Concrete [jk], take longer to initially prime, but after primed, the dispenser performs just fine. Hope that helps!"
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Apr 5, 2014",
         "unixTime":1396681200,
         "question":"What labels are included?",
         "answer":"We have the better living 4 chamber dispenser, but I am guessing the labels are probably the same. We had five labels to choose from-shampoo, conditioner, lotion, soap, and shower gel."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"Oct 16, 2013",
         "unixTime":1381906800,
         "question":"Where can I find replacement bottles?",
         "answer":"I know this is a bit late... Go to www.dispenser.com and look under replacement parts (left side of page). They have bottles for all of their different units."
      },
      {  
         "questionType":"open-ended",
         "asin":"B00004TUBL",
         "answerTime":"May 11, 2014",
         "unixTime":1399791600,
         "question":"How do you prime these? Lost instructions, pumped like 30 times and still not working? Gel comes out no problem but shampoo &amp; conditioner no go?",
         "answer":"Hold your finger over the opening to obstruct it and press the button a few times."
      }
   ]
}